http://www.ceoonline.com.au/about/terms_and_conditions

Search Form
Keywords:
Terms and Conditions
This website is owned and operated by the INTERNATIONAL INSTITUTE OF DIRECTORS AND MANAGERS PTY LIMITED (ABN 26 112 140 299) ("IIDM"). Your access to this website is governed by these Terms and Conditions, Privacy Policy, Copyright Notice, Disclaimer, Links and any other rules and conditions within the website (known collectively as the "Terms of Use"). By using and/or accessing the IIDM website, you agree to be bound by the Terms of Use. Please read them carefully.
Your Membership
By completing and submitting the member registration form on this site, and upon a validation of those details, you will be able to access the various IIDM services. We will provide you with a confirmation notice of your membership which will be emailed to you within 2 business days. We confirm that memberships are not transferable.
Charges
The monthly membership fee to access the IIDM website is US$9.95 (inclusive of GST for Australian members). The annual fee to access the IIDM website is US$99.00 (inclusive of GST for Australian members).
Those charges are payable monthly or annually in advance and will be automatically charged to the nominated credit card details provided by you unless otherwise notified by you. Memberships registered after the 28th day of the month, will be charged to the nominated credit card on the 28th day of the month.
Online payment processing of the membership fee is performed by the secure services provided by VeriSign/PayPal. The security of your credit card details is highly regarded and considered. Should you have any concerns regarding this service, please Contact Us.
New or recurring membership payments processed to your nominated credit card are automatically issued a receipt by VeriSign/PayPal to the member's designated email address.
Termination Of Your Membership
You may terminate your membership at any time. Click on Contact Us and request termination of your membership. No refunds apply.
Security
IIDM makes every possible effort to ensure the security of our members in their dealings with us. This includes, but is not limited to, hosting the IIDM website on encrypted servers, firewall protection and regular monitoring.
We wish to advise that you are responsible for protecting the confidentiality of your login information. You must not make your password available to anyone else. Furthermore, you are responsible for protecting against unauthorised use of your credit card and agree to accept all membership transactions incurred via your password.
Website Content and AccessWhile IIDM endeavours to take reasonable care in preparing and maintaining the information on this website we do not warrant the accuracy, reliability, adequacy or completeness of any of the website content. You acknowledge and accept that the website content may include technical inaccuracies and typographical errors. The website content is subject to change at any time without notice and may not necessarily be up to date or accurate at the time you view it.It is your responsibility to enquire with us directly to ensure the accuracy and currency of the material or information you seek to rely upon. To the extent permitted by law IIDM disclaims all liability for loss directly or indirectly arising from your use of or reliance on the website and the website content.IIDM does not guarantee that access to the IIDM website will be uninterrupted or that the website is free from viruses or anything else which may damage any computer which accesses the IIDM website or any data on such a computer. Our Conditions of Supply
IIDM has the right to change or discontinue any feature of the website including content, hours of availability and equipment required for access.
IIDM will use its reasonable endeavours to ensure that the website and the facilities thereon (including newsletters, personal email and other communication services) is/are available at all times and that the content provided by IIDM is true, accurate and error free.
However, we do not guarantee this and provide no warranties unless specifically stated.
Your Obligations
You must not disclose your login information to anybody or any entity other than IIDM. You must also not store your login information anywhere in which those details could be seen, read or heard by anybody other than IIDM.
You must also not use the IIDM website for any activity whatsoever which in any way breaches any laws, codes or standards. You must also not use the website for any activity which may infringe any third party's rights. You must also not use the IIDM website in any way whatsoever which may be deemed to constitute intimidatory, harassing, menacing, abusive, defamatory or obscene behaviour. In general, you must not send any unsolicited or unwelcome messages or email to anyone using any of the services on the website. You are responsible for obtaining advice about whether your use of the IIDM website breaches any Internet Industry Code(s) of Conduct.
You indemnify IIDM from and against all actions, claims, suits, demands, liabilities, costs or expenses arising out of or in any way connected to the use of the IIDM website by you or any other person using your membership details.
Changes To Your Membership
IIDM may vary the Terms of Use at any time by notice to you. Your continued use of the Service after such notice will constitute acceptance of any variations to the website by us.
If, in IIDM's opinion, you breach any of these Terms of Use, we may terminate your access to the IIDM website and without any entitlement to a refund.
Our Communication Services and Links
The IIDM website includes links to other websites ("Links").
By using any of those Links you agree that:
IIDM is not under any obligation to monitor any of the content contained in the Links.
the views expressed in the Links are not necessarily those of IIDM;
you will not post or transmit any material which contains a virus or other harmful components;
you will not download any material if you know that such material cannot be legally downloaded;
IIDM has a worldwide license to use, copy or adapt any content provided;
you will release IIDM from any liability whatsoever in connection with your use of any of the Links.
Jurisdiction
These Terms of Use will be governed by the laws of the State of Victoria without reference to rules governing choice of laws. Any action relating to these Terms of Use must be brought in the Courts of the State of Victoria.
Disclaimer / Liability
Use of the IIDM website and of all the facilities therein, and any material or information obtained from this website is at your own risk, and IIDM expressly disclaims, to the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, all warranties, expressed or implied, of any kind whatsoever.
In addition, IIDM shall not be responsible for the failure or performance of this website and/or the software used in connection with it; the loss of data or services resulting from delays, non-deliveries, misdeliveries, or service interruptions; the accuracy, quality, timeliness, completeness or nature of information obtained through its services; any omission in the information provided; nor the consequences arising from or related to any viruses transmitted through its services, or any liability, costs, loss of profits or consequential loss arising from your use of, or inability to access this website.
Copyright Notice
All material on this website is either owned or licensed by IIDM or (as warranted) by its licensors, and is protected by intellectual property laws. You may not copy, modify, reproduce, republish, post, transmit or distribute in any way any material from this website including the underlying code and software, save as authorised by these Terms of Use. IIDM reserves the right to sue for breach of its intellectual property rights.
You are only authorised to use this website and its contents for your personal and/or non-commercial use. This amounts to viewing the website and printing off individual pages or sections for personal use. You may not use any part of the material on the website to establish, maintain or aid in the establishment or maintenance of your own publications, internet or other.
In the event you wish to share the website's contents with your peers, staff, friends or clients, we refer you to our Guidelines for Republication of Articles. Alternatively, we recommend registration as a IIDM member in their own right.
Privacy Policy
IIDM is committed to protecting your personal information. We set out below the following important information concerning your privacy:
Collection of Your Personal Information
When you register as a member of IIDM, we will collect details such as your name, organisation, email, job description (and related information). Some of that information is necessary for us to be able to accurately identify the users of our website. Other types of information enable us to profile the users of our particular service. Where designated, information of this type is optional - you do not need to fill it in if you don't wish to.
When you pay for goods or services online using a credit card or PayPal, we collect some additional necessary information, including billing address, credit card number and credit card expiration date. We process your credit card details securely over the Internet using an accredited internet payment security system.
We confirm that IIDM respects the necessity of confidentiality and security of information provided to it by its members and takes reasonable precautions to protect that information from misuse, loss, unauthorised access, modification or disclosure. However, we refer you to the section headed "Security of Your Personal Information" below relating to the security limitations applicable to online transactions.
Use of Your Personal Information
The personal information that you provide to us during registration is used for identification purposes and will assist you using various other services on our website. That information will also assist us to better provide services that tailor your needs. For instance, that information can assist us in finding which areas of the website are most popular.
Information Disclosure
As is required by Law, IIDM is not able to reveal, disclose, sell, distribute, rent, license, share or pass onto any third parties, other than those who are contracted to IIDM and any related entities, any personal information that you have provided to us, unless you have expressly consented for us to do so.
Security of Your Personal Information
Transmissions to and from the IIDM website are monitored for quality control. However, data transmission over the Internet can never be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Whilst we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot insure or warrant its security. Accordingly, these activities are conducted at your own risk.
Accessing, Correcting or Updating Your Personal Information
Information provided to us is kept in a secure environment accessed only by authorised persons. You will always have access to that information and content that you provide to us. You can easily edit your personal information - except for your credit cards details - by accessing the "Amend your details" screen, having previously entered your login information. Credit cards details can be easily updated by clicking on Contact Us and advising us.
Further Security
IIDM recommends that if you have finished your user session that you close your browser. This should be particularly the case if you are using a personal computer which is not owned by you, for example, use in an internet cafe.  Ultimately, the responsibility for security of your information is yours and ours. IIDM also recommends that its members use the various Links carefully.
Links
Mirroring any content from the IIDM website is expressly prohibited without the prior written consent of IIDM.
In general, links to the IIDM website are welcome. Contact IIDM to obtain a copy of their linking policy, prior to establish a link to its website.
Further Contact
If you have any comments, queries or requests, please contact IIDM by telephone, facsimile or click on Contact Us.
International Institute of Directors And Managers Pty Limited (IIDM) ABN 26 112 140 299 1632-1638 High Street Glen Iris Victoria 3146 Australia Telephone: +61 3 9571 6902 Email: online@ceo.com.au Website: www.iidmglobal.com
About Us
Testimonials
Frequently Asked Questions (FAQs)
Why Leadership Matters Most In Managing Difficult Customer Behaviour
Featured Article 1
Why It's Important To Take Ownership For The Way You Lead Your Team
Featured Articles
Why Leadership Matters Most In Managing Difficult Customer Behaviour
Why It's Important To Take Ownership For The Way You Lead Your Team
Four Biochemical Triggers Leaders Can Leverage For Better Engagement
Frequently Asked Questions (FAQs)
ABN 26 112 140 299.
All rights reserved.
Website Design Melbourne Australia by DDSN Interactive
